accuquilt.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire Web Site. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to AccuQuilt Customer Service by e-mail at [info@accuquilt.com](mailto:info@accucut.com) or by mail at 8843 South 137th Circle, Omaha, NE 68138.

**AccuQuilt's Privacy Policy**  
Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. Because we gather certain types of information about AccuQuilt users, we want you to understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it.

**Information that AccuQuilt Gathers**  
AccuQuilt gathers two types of information about users:

  1. **Personal data** , provided through voluntary registration
  2. **Aggregated data** , which tracks users as a whole

**Personal data** may be requested when you sign up for AccuQuilt's personalized services or register for contests, sweepstakes or other promotional programs offered on our service. We ask for this in order to provide you with the best Web experience possible. This information might include member name, password, age, gender, ZIP code and/or country information. Except as described below, it is not disclosed to parties other than AccuQuilt and its parent companies in any way that personally identifies you without your prior permission.

**Aggregated data** , which tracks AccuQuilt user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis, is gathered through several methods.This tracking data follows AccuQuilt traffic in general, and is not used to identify you personally. Aggregated tracking information helps us to determine which areas of our site users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. AccuQuilt does not track what you read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We may disclose such aggregated information to third parties such as our advertisers and partners.

**How AccuQuilt Uses Information**  
AccuQuilt uses any personal information that's voluntarily given by you in order to enhance your experience, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the site or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

AccuQuilt will not disclose any information that personally identifies you to parties other than AccuQuilt and its parent companies without your consent. There are exceptions:

  * When the purpose and manner of disclosure is clearly defined in advance.
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is legally required or to protect our rights.

**Contests and Sweepstakes**  
AccuQuilt occasionally offers contests and sweepstakes in which we request certain personal information on a voluntary basis. These contests and sweepstakes are conducted in full accordance with United States federal and state laws. The full rules and all information about such contests are clearly posted during the event, including how information gathered will be used.

**Search Terms**  
As a measure of user interest, we track search terms that are entered into our site. We create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns to improve shopping and user experiences.

**Cookies and Tracking  
** A cookie is a small data file that Web sites commonly write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file contains information that can identify you anonymously in order to track traffic patterns on our site. The data is encrypted for your added security. AccuCut uses cookies as a way to measure activity on the site in order to continually improve your experience.

Cookies don't identify you personally, but rather identify your computer when you visit our site. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.

Your browser can be set to warn you before accepting cookies. In this case, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You can choose to refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use AccuQuilt, but you will need them for customizable areas of the site. AccuQuilt does allow users to clear cookies.

**Electronic Newsletters**  
AccuQuilt offers free, electronic newsletters as a service to our users, based on a voluntary subscription. You will only receive a newsletter if you have requested it during registration to several areas of AccuQuilt or directly from our sign-up form. We do not share newsletter mailing lists with any third parties unless you voluntarily permit us to do so when you register or sign up.

**Changes to Policy**  
AccuQuilt reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying guests of the existence of a revised privacy policy.

**Opt-Out Policy  
** You may terminate your subscription to our electronic newsletter at any time via e-mail by following the instructions contained at the end of every newsletter.

Currently, AccuQuilt does not offer a means by which to completely delete personal information established at the time of registration for any site. If you have questions about your information, please contact us at [info@accuquilt.com](mailto:info@accucut.com).
